Ezz Elden Mohamed

Front-End Developer

El Mansoura , El Dakahleya | <u>01002368023</u> | <u>ezzelden4work@gmail.com</u>

<u>My WebSite</u>, <u>linkedin</u> , <u>codepen</u> , <u>GitHub</u> , <u>Youtube</u>

Summary

I'm a front-end web developer. I have 5 years of experience in this field. You can say that I'm a full-time Web developer in addition to being a student. I'm passionate about keeping up with everything new in technology trends, I have my personal touch at my work. you can be keen on me for any project you need to do.

Education

I'm Graduated from Delta College of Management Information Systems 2022

Skills

Html | css | Javascript | jQuery | BootStrap | Sass | Vue.js | React.js | React Native | GitHub | CssAnimation | AdobeXD | Figma | Php | WordPress

Professional Experience

<u>Atheltree</u>

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- Survey
- Round Base

Web Instructor: 2021

I was giving some web development courses in my college by assembling groups of students and starting how to develop the website professionally.

Graduation projects Assistant:

2021

I was assisting students in their graduation projects, supervising them in the design and development stages, and discussing them in front of a specialized committee of doctors in the fields of technology.

Some of Project:

- Elfahd Elevetor
- Smart Parking
- Elkepash

The Lean

Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

• Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- Store Demo
- Youssef Allam Group
- Khozam

Afro Arab Digital

Feb 2020 - July 2020

• Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- Afro Arab Digital
- Bakkahlean

Devolum

Oct 2017 - Feb 2020

Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- Alemnishokran
- Midstr
- Islah
- Oral

Projects

Vuesax Dashboard

gitHub Live View

Dark & Light Mode

• Chat Page

Round Base <u>gitHub</u> <u>Live View</u>

- React.js
- Company Review

Elkebash Site <u>Live View</u>

- WordPress
- Ui/Ux

See More Projects.....

Langues

Arabic : Native | English : Good Write and Speak